A Guide to the University of Virginia Advisory Committee on the Concerns of Handicapped Persons, 1976-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Advisory Committee on the Concerns of Handicapped Persons 1976-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-20/82/1.911
This collection consists of 5 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 May 21.
Contents List
- Association on Handicapped Student Service Programs in Post-Secondary Education (AHSSPPE) Conference 1988 (Box 1)
- Articles in University Publications 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Budget and Finance 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Career Planning and Placement 1987-1988 (Box 1)
- Correspondence--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 1)
- Correspondence----Handicapped Access 1989 (Box 1)
- Disabled Services--San Diego State University 1988 (Box 1)
- Disabled Services--State University of New York Manuals n.d. (Box 1)
- Disabled Services--University of Illinois 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Disabled Services--University of Maryland 1985-1988 (Box 2)
- Disabled Services--Wisconsin-Whitewater 1982, n.d. (Box 2)
- Equipment (2 folders) 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Establishing the Committee 1988 (Box 2)
- Forums 1988 (Box 2)
- Guidelines and Standards n.d. (Box 2)
- Handicapped Committee Agenda 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Health Sciences Division 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Hearing Impairments 1988 (Box 2)
- Idea File 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Keeling, Richard P.--Letter 1988 December (Box 2)
- Law School--Handicapped Access 1988-1989 (Box 3)
- Laws and Legal Implications 1984-1988 (Box 3)
- Legal Statutes, Acts and Articles n.d. (Box 3)
- Learning Disabilities 1982-1989 (Box 3)
- McGee, Kathy--Dissertation Survey 1988 (Box 3)
- Meeting Minutes 1988 (Box 3)
- Meeting Notes and Agendas 1988 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 3)
- O'Neil, Robert M. 1983-1987 (Box 3)
- --Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 3)
- Parking 1988 (Box 4)
- President's Retreat--University of Virginia 1988 September (Box 4)
- Printed-- The Times1987 December (Box 4)
- Problems and Letters 1988 (Box 4)
- Programs at Other Institutions (3 folders) 1984-1989 (Box 4)
- Publicity 1988 (Box 4)
- Resources for Working With Handicapped Persons 1976-1988 (Box 4)
- Sexuality Problems of Handicapped 1987-1988 (Box 5)
- Special Problems of Disabled People 1977-1987 (Box 5)
- Stillfried, Mr. and Mrs. Dominik 1988-1989 (Box 5)
- Student Council 1988 (Box 5)
- Subcommittees 1988-1989 (Box 5)
- Tape Cassettes 1988, n.d. (Box 5)
- Technology 1987-1988 (Box 5)
- Travel by Disabled Persons 1987-1988 (Box 5)
- University of Virginia--Handicapped Papers (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 5)
- University of Virginia--Survey of Disabled Students 1986 (Box 5)
- Visual Impairments n.d. (Box 5)
- Whiting, Stephen 1989 (Box 5)